Hi everyone, how are you? Welcome to another jumpsuit up here on my channel.
And today I'm going to show you a super cool activewear jumpsuit from a Russian
brand called Fluido. This one is special because I have not seen a catsuit with
so many panels and such a complex pattern so far. So without further ado
I'm going to change into it so I can show you more of it
I
I love this fit and this pattern and the cut of it. It almost feels and is constructed like a corset that's integrated here with all these single panels here.
also on the back side so I don't know if I want to count them, the panels, like 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22,
23, 24, something around about 24, 25 panels for one catsuit. I think that's a new record.
If I think back to the Winterfötisch catsuit, that cut was awesome and also
yeah very detailed but I think this one is even more detailed and I don't know.
I like it it looks so good it feels so good it's so comfy it's available in
different colors but with the black here there is a contrast stitching going on
with white and I think that really emphasizes this cut again so I don't
know when I would see this I wouldn't think of active wear also combined with
the heels doesn't really look like active wear and I learned one thing you
You know I always complain that catsuits are too short, the arms are too short, the legs are too short.
I found the solution for me. I have to shop in Russia or order from Russian brands
because apparently they have different cuts than the rest of Europe or Asia
and all the Russian sportwear or activewear stuff fits me so good because it's so long.
If you have the same problem than me you may want to check them out.
Okay, I want to do a different styling, a second look with a leather jacket and some different heels. Let's go.
Okay, completely different look I guess.
I think I like it better with the jacket closed.
look like a sports outfit at all anymore.
But it's also nice. You can also close it up. No, I'm going to open it again because I think it's too much.
That's better.
Yeah, I don't know, I like this look.
I think it has something casual with the leather jacket.
And the over-knee thigh-high boots balance that out again.
Which look do you prefer, the first or the second?
Leave a comment down below.
Click on the thumbs up button, subscribe to my channel
and check out my Patreon if you want to support this video.
Fun fact, I did a poll on Patreon
and they basically decided that I'm going to buy this catsuit.
So yeah, you should check it out.
See you around.
Have a nice day.
Bye.